isocpp.org 2017-02-20

# Privacy Policy : Standard C++

## Privacy Policy

##  Personal Information

Personal information submitted on this site is used by Standard C++ Foundation solely for the purpose stated to you at the time of submission, including to operate and improve the site and for statistical analysis. We do not give your personal information to anyone else, unless it is necessary to do so in order to provide the service requested by you (including sharing to the extent necessary with third parties that the Foundation hires to perform limited services on its behalf, such as hosting and support) and we have made a full disclosure to you, or we have good faith belief that disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to satisfy any applicable laws or regulations or to detect and prevent fraud, security, or technical issues. Any personal information submitted will not be sold, traded, or rented under any circumstances.

##  E-mail Address

The e-mail address that you supply when creating an account on this site will be used to contact you regarding your account (for example, if you forget your user name or password and request assistance with logging in, assistance will be provided by means of a message sent to the e-mail address entered in your user profile), or for critical updates and notifications (such as a material change in the privacy policy).

##  Cookies

Cookies are used to remember preferences that are chosen by you when using this site. No personal information is collected by or stored in cookies.

##  No Ad Networks

This site does not participate in ad networks.

##  Product Information

This site transmits product information through the "Product News" RSS feed category, and no more than once a week in a directly C++-related "sponsored message" in the main RSS feed.

##  Scripting/JavaScript

We use scripting to improve the functionality of this site, such as to add color and formatting to source code examples and to return information more quickly to you. Scripting is never used to install software on your computer or to collect unauthorized information from you.

You should enable JavaScript for this site in your browser to enable some portions of the site to work properly. Most browsers let you enable or disable this feature for specific sites. Consult your browser's help documentation to learn how to enable scripting for selected sites.

##  Updates

If it is ever necessary to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect and how we use it.

_Updated 2012-10-26_
